{
    "subject": "resource/Dualesc",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Dualesc's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9664799571037292,
            "question": "Does Dualesc currently reside in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9052461385726929,
            "question": "Is the United States a significant location for Dualesc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8619537353515625,
            "question": "Is Dualesc originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8509835600852966,
            "question": "What country is considered Dualesc's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.828750729560852,
            "question": "Could Dualesc be considered a citizen of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6767029166221619,
            "question": "Where is Dualesc from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5302268266677856,
            "question": "What are some aspects of Dualesc's life that might be influenced by being from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5169219970703125,
            "question": "Where did Dualesc grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4987199306488037,
            "question": "What nationality is Dualesc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24863694608211517,
            "question": "What is the name of the place that Dualesc calls home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dualesc's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9304_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Dualesc?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9304_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Dualesc grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9304_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some aspects of Dualesc's life that might be influenced by being from the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9304_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9304_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that there is no mention of a person named Dualesc or their hometown in the provided context information. The documents only discuss products, music bands, and locations related to Portland and Eugene, but do not provide any information about a person named Dualesc or their background."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document does not provide any information about a product or entity named \"Dualesc\" or its hometown. The closest related content discusses radio products like the DX3C and DX3R, but there is no mention of a \"Dualesc\" or its location."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Dualesc is not a tangible entity such as a person or place, but rather a product (DX3C radio), and it does not have a hometown.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of a location named \"Dualesc\" or any information about its hometown within the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no information about Dualesc's hometown being the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context does not provide any information about Dualesc's hometown. Moreover, the given text discusses the Scorpion Nano and other products or entities, none of which are related to Dualesc, making it impossible to deduce its origin based on the provided information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}